<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-07-05T18:27:50+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Cloud Market Research</title><subtitle>How big is the cloud market region-wise, and how has it changed over time?&lt;/b&gt; Interactive visualization of regional market share since 2016. 
</subtitle><author><name>Cloud Market Research</name></author><entry><title type="html">Cloud Market Research</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/machine/learning/cloudMarketResearch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cloud Market Research" /><published>2022-02-21T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-02-21T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/machine/learning/cloudMarketResearch</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/machine/learning/cloudMarketResearch.html">&lt;p&gt;Report: How market cap of big 3 cloud solutions has changed over time
Meta: How big is the cloud market region-wise, and how has it changed over time? Interactive visualization of regional market share since 2015&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The fact that the cloud infrastructure market enjoyed another exceptional quarter is not breaking news. Following the prominent three vendors’ earnings reports this week, Amazon, Microsoft, and Google, who together captured 65% of worldwide cloud computing spending in Q1 2022, surpassed their competition to the point where their combined dominance limits competitors from pursuing specialized markets.
If you’re anything like me, you might be curious about the regional market size for each platform. What about the number of businesses utilizing these services locally? How well do these services return on investment?
But what about the regions
Although the regional market study is heavily understudied and speculative, we still conducted exhaustive research that led to fascinating insights about many regions’ prominent three vendors’ market cap. 
We essentially utilized multiple prominent features, which will allow us to predict the market cap for various regions of the top three cloud vendors. We presented our findings via interactive visualization shown below. 
Visualization
Let’s Dive deep
Case Study 1: 
Both AWS and Azure are seeing an increase in income from year to year. Compared to the same quarter the year before, AWS and Azure earnings have increased in a given quarter. Because not all businesses provide a detailed revenue breakdown, it is impossible to compare their cloud revenue like-for-like. However, Azure had the highest year-over-year (YoY) cloud revenue growth in Q4 2021, at 50%. Google Cloud came in second place with a 45 percent share, and AWS came in third with a 32 percent YoY revenue increase. Although Azure continues to close the gap in many locations, it is almost probable that AWS will maintain the top spot in terms of overall revenue this quarter. 
Case Study 2
Magnum Corporation has been a pioneer in Malaysia’s gaming sector since 1968. The company’s primary areas of interest include its legally permitted lottery business, 4-Digit (4D) numbers forecast betting, and related activities. The company’s on-site, co-located IT infrastructure was handled by an internal team answering the CIO. It is hosted in Kuala Lumpur. In light of the shifting business climate and market circumstances in Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this period, it had to host its Microsoft-based packaging and logistics systems effectively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since their user base was dispersed around the APAC area, this had to be done without causing service interruptions or accessibility issues.
The organization began its cloud migration by implementing the SaaS mail service O365. But they also had to organize, design, and manage their PaaS (Platform as a Service) and IaaS (Infrastructure as a Service) clouds. They intended to eventually embrace Microsoft Azure to create an internal cloud center of excellence since they required a reliable partner to help them with their cloud transition and score some quick victories.
Case study 3
An E-commerce solution provider founded in 2015, the client intends to simplify the rapidly evolving landscape of online commerce for hyperlocal businesses through their sustainable and simple solutions. Based in Bengaluru, the client has grown across many countries powering hundreds of point-of-sale(POS) companies and thousands of restaurants across the world. Previous application setup which is hosted on AWS, the tech stack and their dependencies with other applications and components.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Firm migrated from AWS to GCP in order to leverage Google Cloud Platform benefits, reduce cost consumption, and meet business needs.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Mrityunjay</name></author><category term="Cloud" /><category term="Regional" /><category term="Market Cap" /><category term="Interactive" /><category term="Visualization" /><category term="Threejs" /><summary type="html">Report: How market cap of big 3 cloud solutions has changed over time Meta: How big is the cloud market region-wise, and how has it changed over time? Interactive visualization of regional market share since 2015</summary></entry></feed>